Second, 2024.
Mr. President General, are you okay?
I'm in a minute.
I'd like to leave you to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation under God, into his soul, with liberty of justice for all.
Four public input unscheduled personal parenthesis.
Five, five minutes.
Motion to approve.
Second.
of you for the $4,920.050. This is for the expert review and report fee for Dr. Liu
Special Master from 11423 to 112823. So, I have the 750,000 budget for the GRDA claims.
The current balance is $572,355.084 for the remainder of this fiscal year if the current
invoice of $4,922.050.050 is approved and paid. This will leave a balance of $567,433.034.040.
So, clearly we have it up in the fiscal year budget for this fiscal year. However, to clarify
additionally, of the original $300,000 that was approved by the Council on September 2nd of
2008 for civil litigation costs involving GRDA, the current balance is $58,745.050.
If the current invoicing totaling $49,920,050 is approved and paid, it will leave remaining
balance of the civil litigation in the amount of $53,823.040.040.040.
Clear as mud. So, the difference that you're seeing tonight is that $300,000 which we generally
do not talk about because we don't have claims that hit that $300,000 approved back in 2008. However,
they are out of point in the civil litigation where they were required.
higher special master and that was part of the original agreement 2008 that the city would
front that cost. So that's why we're finally seeing this. It's been that many years but
here we are at that point again and if you need a better definition of a special master, I'll
have to let Ben better clarify that.
Tell us, man.
Well, simply a special master is expert from that area. So this individual will be reviewing
all the reports from tide and theirs on their side. Reviews all this for the judge and
then the sign for it so that the judge can understand it. The person is impartial. They're
pointed, they're selected by both sides of reading on that something has to pay the cost
of that and so both sides pay the cost of having a special master. And they're all undoubtedly
be more expensive in this point. But the good thing is this is a clear indication that
it's coming to a hit.
In the civil litigation, the civil issue is the civil issue.
The litigation set in play. The litigants that actually got flooded in the Northland board.
Correct.
Yes.
Well, sir.
Thank you. Motion. We approve.
Hi.
Hey. They've just arrived from Maine, Claim, for Pensacola, Jordanian, and he relies on seeing associated
point, perceived in about $9,671.30.
So again, you've got this BA in your packet tonight for professional services and disbursements
incurred from November 1st, 2023 through November 29th, 2023 on behalf of the city of Mayma.
This invoice focused on review of pleadings, filings and other documentation, preparing responses.
They're too communicating with my obtained relating to the dam, safety issues, the relaxing
things study plan.
the contaminated sediment transport study, the enough amendment, and the circuit court of appeals
follow-up. The 750 budgeted fiscal year, the current balance, is $567,433.34. The current
invoice of $9,671.30 is approved. It would leave this fiscal year balance to be $557,760
dollars and $4 cents, so we do have plenty budgeted fiscal year for this invoice, especially
a group.
Thank you.
Hi.
The new business of any of which has risen since the post of this agenda, can't task staff reports.
We'll have an custody committee announcements. 12 adjourned.
Thank you.
Hi.